RBRL/082/GGA
Richard B. Russell Library for Political Research and Studies
- III. Member Files, 1971-2006; 8.0 boxes; (8 linear feet)
  - A. Biographical Files, 1975-2004; 295.0 folders
    - Henrietta Turnquest, [November 16, 1995 – May 8, 2002] (Box III.3, Folder 37)
    - Ralph Twiggs, –March 3, 1989 – January 22, 2004] (Box III.3, Folder 38)
    - Ted Waddle, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 39)
    - Kenneth Waldrop, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 40)
    - Charles Walker, [September 21, 1989] (Box III.3, Folder 41)
    - Larry Walker, [February 10, 1988 – July 15, 2002] (Box III.3, Folder 42)
    - Vinson Wall, [December 21, 1988 – October 25, 1993] (Box III.3, Folder 43)
    - Crawford Ware, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 44)
    - Charlie Watts, [May 23, 1984 – February 22, 1996] (Box III.3, Folder 45)
    - Jack West, [August 5, 1999 – January 9, 2001] (Box III.3, Folder 46)
    - Lynn Westmoreland, [June 3, 1999] (Box III.3, Folder 47)
    - John White, [January 13, 1995 – February 17, 1995] (Box III.3, Folder 48)
    - Benjamin Whitaker, [May 29, 1995 – August 28, 1998] (Box III.3, Folder 49)
    - Tim Wilder, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 50)
    - John J. Wiles, [January 28, 1997 – February 27, 1998] (Box III.3, Folder 51)
    - Betty Jo Williams, [August 14, 1995 – January 23, 1997] (Box III.3, Folder 52)
    - Jeff Williams, [May 29, 1995 – August 1, 2002] (Box III.3, Folder 53)
    - Robin Williams, [August 14, 1995 – August 5, 1999] (Box III.3, Folder 54)
    - Joe Wilson, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 55)
    - Joe Wood, [January 30, 1985] (Box III.3, Folder 56)
    - Jim Woods, [February 3, 1995 – February 9, 1996] (Box III.3, Folder 57)
    - Ken Workman, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 58)
    - Rene Unterman, [June 3, 1999 – June 15, 2001] (Box III.3, Folder 59)
    - Charles Yeargin, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 60)
  - B. Photographs, 1985-2004; 3135 photographs, 3 negatives, and 4 slides
    This sub-series is arranged alphabetically and includes black and white and color photographs and negatives of members of the Georgia House of Representatives. These photographs have been removed from the Biographical Files for the purpose of preservation. Additional photographs of House members and events are located in Series VII: Photographs.
    - Betty Aaron, [Portraits, 1 (2.25x2.25) b/w] (Box III.4, Folder 1)
    - Ralph David Abernathy, [Portraits, 5 (5x7) b/w] (Box III.4, Folder 2)
    - G. D. Adams, [Portraits, 15 (various sizes) b/w; 8 (8x10) color; pictures, 11 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 3)
    - Marvin Adams, [Portraits, 10 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 12 (8x10) color; pictures, 15 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 4)
    - Fred Aiken, [Portraits, 10 (5x7) b/w; 9 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 5)
    - Dean Alford, [Portraits, 2 (5x7 and 8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 6)
    - Ray Allen, [Portraits, 5 (various sizes) b/w; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 7)
    - Wendell T. Anderson, [Portraits, 8 (various sizes); 11 (8x10) color; pictures, 13 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 8)
    - Bob Argo, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) b/w; 11 (4x5 and 8x10) color; pictures (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 9)
    - Troy Athon, [Portraits, 7 (various sizes) b/w; 10 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 10)
    - Bill Atkins, [Negatives, 1] (Box III.4, Folder 11)
    - Dean Auten, [Portraits, 7 (various sizes) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 5 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 12)
    - Frank Bailey, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 13)
    - Ralph James Balkcom, [Portraits, 17 (3.5x5, 5x7, 8x10) b/w; 7 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 14)
    - Charles Banister, [Portraits, 5 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 3 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 15)
    - Fisher Barfoot, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 16)
    - Emory E. Bargerson, [Portraits, 10 (5x7) b/w; 8 (8x10) color; pictures, 7 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 1 (3.5x5) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 17)
    - Bill Barnett, [Portraits, 8 (various sizes) b/w; 8 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w; 6 (5x7) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 18)
    - Mike Barnett, [Portraits, 11 (5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 19)
    - James Beck, [Portraits, 10 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color, pictures, 6 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 20)
    - Jimmy Benefield, [Portraits, 12 (4x5 and 8x10) color; 3 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; pictures, 4 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 21)
    - Lorenzo Benn, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (5x7) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 22)
    - Ken Birdsong, [Portraits, 12 (various sizes) b/w; 13 (8x10) color; pictures, 12 (5x7) b/w, 1(4x5) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 23)
    - Sanford Bishop, [Portraits, 4 (4x5 and 5x7) b/w; 13 (4x5 and 8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 24)
    - Paul Bolster, [Portraits, 15, (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 9 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 25)
    - Henry Bostick, [Portraits, 8 (various sizes) b/w; 10 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 26)
    - Paul Branch, [Portraits, 16 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 7 (2.5x3.5 and 8x10) color; pictures, 4 (5x7) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 27)
    - Claude Bray, [Portraits, 10 (various sizes) b/w; 13 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 28)
    - Keith Breedlove, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 29)
    - George Brown, [Portraits, 5 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 30)
    - Thomas Buck, [Portraits, 14 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 9 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 31)
    - Floyd Buford, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 32)
    - Roger Byrd, [Portraits, 14 (various sizes) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7) b/w; 1 ( 8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 33)
    - Tyrone Carrell, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 34)
    - Hanson Carter, [Portraits, 7 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 35)
    - Donald E. Cheeks, [Portraits, 11 (3.5x5, 5x7 8x10) b/w; 4 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 36)
    - Tommy Chambless, [Portraits, 14 (various sizes) b/w; 11(8x10) color; pictures, 11 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 37)
    - George Chance, [Portraits, 10 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 6 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 38)
    - Peggy Childs, [Pictures, 4 (5x7), 1 developed negative, b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 39)
    - Buddy Childers, [Portraits, 1 (8x10) b/w; 4 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 40)
    - Betty Clark, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (8x10) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 41)
    - Louis Clark, [Portraits, 8 (various sizes) b/w; 19 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (various sizes) b/w; 5 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 42)
    - Luther Colbert, [Portraits, 5 (various sizes) b/w; 13 (8x10) color; pictures, 11 (various sizes) b/w; 1 (3.5x5) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 43)
    - Jack Connell, [Portraits, 13 (various sizes) b/w; 13 (8x10) color; pictures, 7 (5x7) b/w, 3 (8x10) color.] (Box III.4, Folder 44)
    - Bill Cooper, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 45)
    - Barbara Couch, [Portraits, 4 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 1(8x10) color; pictures, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 46)
    - Walter Cox, [Portraits, 9 (4x5 and 5x7) b/w; 12 (8x10) color; pictures, 4 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 47)
    - John G. Crawford, [Portraits, 7 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 14 (8x10) color; pictures, 16 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.4, Folder 48)
    - Tom Crosby, [Portraits, 8 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 12 (8x10) color; pictures, 8 (5x7) b/w; 3 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 1)
    - Mary Young Cummings, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 2)
    - Grace Davis, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; pictures, (3.5x5) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 3)
    - Max Davis, [Pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 4)
    - Douglas Dean, [Portraits, 9 (various sizes) b/w; 9 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 5)
    - Harry Dixon, [Portraits, 17 (various sizes) b/w; 8 (8x10) color; pictures, 7 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 6)
    - Denny Dobbs, [Portraits, 8 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 7)
    - Bill Dover, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w; 5 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 8)
    - Ward Elliot, [Portraits, 13 (various sizes) b/w; 13 (8x10) color; pictures, 14 (various sizes) b/w; 3 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 9)
    - Lawton Evans, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 10)
    - Dorothy Felton, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 3 (8x10) color; pictures, 11 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 11)
    - Jimmy Floyd, [Portraits, 5 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 12)
    - Phil Foster, [Portraits, 6 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 13)
    - Mary Jane Galer, [Portraits, 12 (various sizes) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 10 (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 14)
    - John Godbee, [Portraits, 8 (various sizes) b/w; 5 (8x10) color; pictures, 10 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 15)
    - Tim Golden, [Pictures, 1 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 16)
    - Willard Goodwin, [Portraits, 7 (5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 17)
    - George Green, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 18)
    - John W. Greet, [Portraits, 9 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 2 (8x10) color; pictures, 4 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 1 (3.5x5) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 19)
    - William Gresham, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 20)
    - Jim Griffin, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 21)
    - Denmark Grover, [Portraits, 10 (various sizes) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 22)
    - DeWayne Hamilton, [Portraits, 6 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 23)
    - Bobby Harris, [Picture, 1 (3.5x5) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 24)
    - Jed Harris, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 25)
    - Bill Hasty, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 15 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (various sizes) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 26)
    - Paul Heard, [Portraits, 7 (4.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color; pictures, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 27)
    - Sam Hensley, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 28)
    - James Hill, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 29)
    - Ray Holland, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 30)
    - Frank Horne, [Portraits, 13 (various sizes) b/w; 13 (8x10) color; pictures, 8 5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 31)
    - Charles Gresham Howren, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 32)
    - Newt Hudson, [Portraits, 2 (3.5x5 and 5x7); 11 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 33)
    - Johnny Isakson, [Portraits, 7 (4.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 10 (4.5x5 and 8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 34)
    - Bill Jackson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 35)
    - Jerry Jackson, [Portraits, 7 (various sizes) b/w; 7 (8x10) color; pictures, 17 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 36)
    - Neal Jackson, [Portraits, 4 (various sizes) b/w; pictures, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 37)
    - Diane Johnson, [Portraits, 2 (4.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 38)
    - Rudolph Johnson, [Portraits, 2 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 39)
    - Suzi Johnson, [Portraits, 6 (5x7) b/w; 3 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 40)
    - Tom Kilgore, [Portraits, 14 (various sizes) b/w; 14 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 41)
    - Jack Kingston, [Portraits, 5 (3.5x5 5x7) b/w; 2 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 42)
    - Dick Lane, [Portraits, 3 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 14 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 43)
    - Terry Lawler, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 44)
    - Tom Lawrence, [Portraits, 7 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 9 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 45)
    - Robert Lawson, [Portraits, 7 (various sizes) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 46)
    - Bill Lee, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 7 (8x10) color; pictures, 7 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 1 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 47)
    - Carolyn Lee, [Portraits, 4 (8x10) color; 1 (3.5x5) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 48)
    - John Linder, [Portraits, 4 (5x7) b/w; 3 (8x10) color; pictures, (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 49)
    - Bobby Long, [Portraits, 8 (various sizes) b/w; 7 (8x10) color; pictures, 18 (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 50)
    - John Lupton, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 51)
    - J. C. Maddox, [Portraits, 6 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 52)
    - George Maddox, [Pictures, 1 (8x10) color.] (Box III.5, Folder 53)
    - Bill Mangum, [Portraits, 5 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 14 (8x10) color; pictures, 13 (8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 54)
    - Charles Martin, [Portraits, 6 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 14 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 55)
    - Hugh Matthews, [Portraits, 8 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 15 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (8x10) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 56)
    - Bubba McDonald, [Portraits, 6 (2.5x3.5 and 3.5x5) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.5, Folder 57)
    - Billy McKinney, [Portraits, 1 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 1)
    - Forrest McKelvey, [Portraits, 7 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 2)
    - Anne Meuller, [Portraits, 7 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 3)
    - Billy Milford, [Pictures, (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 4)
    - Debra Mills, [Portraits, (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 5)
    - John Mobley, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 6)
    - Lunsford Moody, [Portraits, 5 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 5 (8x10) color; pictures, (5x7, 5x8, 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 7)
    - James Moore, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 11 (8x10) color; pictures, 8 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 8)
    - Chesley Morton, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, 4 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 9)
    - John Mostiler, [Portraits, 7 (various sizes) b/w; 8 (8x10) color; pictures, (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 10)
    - Roy Moultrie, [Portraits, 7 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 5 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 11)
    - Tom Murphy, [Portraits, 3 (8x10) b/w, 4 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 12)
    - Donald Oliver, [Portraits, 2 (3.5x5) b/w; 3 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 13)
    - Mike Padgett, [Portraits, 6 (various sizes) b/w; 14 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 14)
    - James Pannell, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 1 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 15)
    - Larry Parrish, [Portraits, 5 (3.5x5 and 5x6) b/w; 3 (8x0) color; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w; 2 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 16)
    - Bob Patten, [Portraits, 6 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 16 (8x10) color; pictures, 17 (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 17)
    - Robert Peters, [Portraits, 4 (5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 3 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 18)
    - Boyd Pettit, [Portraits, 5 (3.5x5 and 5x6) b/w; 8 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 19)
    - Pete Phillips, [Portraits, 4 (various sizes) b/w; 8 (8x10) color; pictures, 15 (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 20)
    - Frank Pinkston, [Portraits, 1 (8x10) color; pictures, 4 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 21)
    - Ron Pittman, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 22)
    - Charles Poag, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 23)
    - Allyn Prichard, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 24)
    - Howard Rainey, [Portraits, 5 (8x10) color; 6 (5x7) b/w; pictures, (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 25)
    - Tom Ramsey, [Portraits, 9 (various sizes) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 15 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Ramsey, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 27)
    - Billy Randall, [Portraits, 5 (5x7) b/w; 7 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 1 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 28)
    - Dick Ransom, [Portraits, 6 (5x7) b/w; 2 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 29)
    - Henry Reaves, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 7 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 30)
    - Frank Redding, [Portraits, 4 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 31)
    - Eleanor Richardson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 32)
    - Edward Ricketson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 33)
    - Cas Robinson, [Portraits, 14 (various sizes) b/w; 11 (4.5x5 and 8x10) color; pictures, 9 (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 34)
    - Pete Robinson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 35)
    - Barron Ross, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 9 (8x10) color; pictures, 6 (8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 36)
    - Randy Sauder, [Portraits, 4 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 37)
    - J. Neal Shepard, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 12 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 38)
    - Allen Sherrod, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 9 (8x10) color; pictures, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 39)
    - John Simpson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 40)
    - Earleen Sizemore, [Portraits, 3 (5x7 b/w; 1 (8x10) color; pictures, 12 (various sizes) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 41)
    - Larry Smith, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 4 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 42)
    - Willow Smith, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 43)
    - Mike Snow, [Portraits, 4 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 44)
    - Frank Stancil, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w; 3 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 45)
    - Cathey W. Steinberg, [Portraits, 9 (5x7) b/w; 12 (8x10) color; pictures, 7 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 46)
    - Charles Thomas, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, (5x8 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 47)
    - Kil Townsend, [Portraits, 5 (5x7) b/w; 11 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 48)
    - Tom Triplett, [Portraits, 8 (3.5x5, 5x7, 8x10) b/w; 3 (8x10) color; pictures, 3 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 49)
    - Ralph Twiggs, [Portraits, 5 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 11 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 50)
    - Ted Waddle, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 9 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 51)
    - Kenneth Waldrop, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 52)
    - Charles Walker, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 10 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 53)
    - Larry Walker, [Portraits, 10 (4.5x5, 5x7, 8x10) b/w; 8 (8x10) color; pictures, 27 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 54)
    - Vinson Wall, [Portraits, 3 (8x10) color; pictures, 16 (5x7 and 810) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 55)
    - Vinson Wall, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 2 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 56)
    - Crawford Ware, [Portraits, 12 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 15 (8x10) color; pictures, 10 (5x7 and 8x10) b/w; 3 (3.5x5) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 57)
    - Charlie Watts, [Portraits, 5 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 58)
    - John White, [Portraits, 10 (various sizes) b/w; 13 (8x10) color; pictures, 9 (8x10) b/w; 4 color slides] (Box III.6, Folder 59)
    - Betty Jo Williams, [Portraits, 7 (various sizes) b/w; 3 (8x10) color; pictures, 2 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 60)
    - Juanita Williams, [Portraits, 8 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 2 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 61)
    - Joe Wilson, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w; 6 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7 8x10) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 62)
    - Joe Wood, [Portraits, 11 (various sizes) b/w; 10 (8x10) color; pictures, 14 95x7 and 8x10) b/w; 3 (4.5x5) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 63)
    - Ken Workman, [Portraits, 4 (various sizes) b/w; 2 (8x10) color; pictures, 5 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.6, Folder 64)
    - Charles Yeargin, [Portraits, 8 (3.5x5 and 5x7) b/w; 9 (8x10) color.] (Box III.6, Folder 65)
    - House Chairman, House Offices (folder 1 of 2), [Portraits, 36 (8x10) color] (Box III.7, Folder 1)
    - House Chairman, House Offices (folder 2 of 2), [Portraits, 33 (8x10) color, 13 (3.5x5) b/w] (Box III.7, Folder 2)
    - Interior House Chamber, [24 (various sizes) b/w; 32 (8x10) color; 35 mm color] (Box III.7, Folder 3)
    - Speakers Office (Folder 1 of 5), [Portraits, 32 (various sizes) b/w; 9 color.] (Box III.7, Folder 4)
    - Speakers Office (Folder 2 of 5), [Portraits, 30 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.7, Folder 5)
    - Speakers Office (Folder 3 of 5), [Portraits, 29 (5x7) b/w; 3 (5x7) color.] (Box III.7, Folder 6)
    - Speakers Office (Folder 4 of 5), Speakers Office [Portraits, 30 (5x7) b/w; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.7, Folder 7)
    - Speakers Office (Folder 5 of 5), Speakers Office [Portraits, 31 (4.5x5 and 5x7) color; 3 (4.5x5 and 5x7) b/w.] (Box III.7, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, [Pictures, 18 (8x10) color.] (Box III.7, Folder 9)
    - Representatives (Folder 1 of 3), [Portraits, 30 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.7, Folder 10)
    - Representatives (Folder 2 of 3), [Portraits, 30 (5x7) b/w.] (Box III.7, Folder 11)
    - Representatives (Folder 3 of 3), [Portraits, 1 (8x10) b/w; 20 (various sizes) color; pictures, 3 (3.5x5.5) color.] (Box III.7, Folder 12)
    - Jimmy Carter, [Pictures, 17 (8x10) color.] (Box III.7, Folder 13)
    - House In Session, [Pictures, 15 (8x10) color.] (Box III.7, Folder 14)
    - Herman Talmadge, [Pictures, 30 (8x10) color.] (Box III.7, Folder 15)
  - C. Directories, 1971-2006; 15.0 folders
    This sub-series includes fifteen photo directories of the members of the Georgia General Assembly from 1971 to 2006; gaps exist for years 1979 to 1982, 1985 to 1986, and 2001 to 2004.
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1971-1972 Term] (1 Copy) (Box III.8, Folder 1)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1973-1974 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 2)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1975-1976 Term] (2 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 3)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1977-1978 Term] (2 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 4)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1983-1984 Term] (2 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 5)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1987-1988 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 6)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1989-1990 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 7)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1991-1992 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 8)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1993-1994 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 9)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1995-1996 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 10)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1997-1998 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 11)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 1999-2000 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 12)
    - [State Senate and House of Representatives Members, 2005-2006 Term] (3 Copies) (Box III.8, Folder 13)
    - [Color Brochure Master], undated (Box III.8, Folder 14)
    - [Georgia House of Representatives] (3 copies), undated (Box III.8, Folder 15)
- IV. Speech Files, 1975-2003; 1.0 box; 1 box and 1 electronic file (1 linear foot)
  This series contains eighty-three speech files arranged alphabetically by topic. These speeches, maintained by the communications office, are intended to assist members with the creation of presentations. The speeches deal with various topics related to Georgia including education, forestry, medicine, transportation, taxes, and women in business. A majority of these speeches are undated and unassociated with a particular member.